我刚买下了这房子 我要把它送给钱德
I just bought this house, and I'm gonna give it to Chandler.
-真的吗？-假的
-Really? - No.
但是 我要把它给一个送披萨的人 这是怎么做的
But, I am gonna give it to a pizza delivery guy, and here's how.
我们点了披萨
We ordered a pizza.
多米诺比萨饼 我能为您效劳吗？
Domino's Pizza, how can I help you?
我可以要一个意大利香肠吗？请送货
Can I have a pepperoni? Delivery, please.
然后我们雇了一个送披萨的人帮我们搬了一整天家具
Then we paid a pizza delivery guy to help us move furniture all day.
我们只需要帮忙搬家具
We just need help moving furniture.
如果我们给你几千美元
If we were to give you a few thousand dollars,
你能帮我们搬一整天家具吗？
could you just help us move furniture all day?
当然 -真的吗？
Sure. - Really?
我们只告诉他我们是年轻人 我们需要一个额外的手动家具
All we told him is that we are YouTubers and we needed an extra hand moving furniture.
因为我们的朋友查德下岗了 我们真的很想帮助他
Because our friend Chad got laid off, and we really wanted to help him.
但他不知道 查德不是真的
But little does he know, Chad isn't real.
最后我们会
At the end of the day we would actually
把房子的100%所有权给他
give him 100% ownership of the house
他正在帮我们搬家具
he is helping us move furniture into.
恶作剧！-找到他了
Pranked! - Got him.
令人惊讶的是 他也同意
Surprisingly, he's going along with it.
他以为他只得到几千美元
All he thinks he's getting is a few thousand dollars.
把家具搬进去后 我们会说 “这把钥匙是你的 ”
After we move all the furniture in, we're just gonna be like, "This key is yours. "
好吧 去沃尔玛
All right, to Walmart it is.
我们只是想填满他的房子
We're trying to just fill his house.
家具也是
So furniture.
我们从卧室开始吧
So let's start in the bedroom.
哦 宝贝
Oh, baby.
你觉得这样的椅子怎么样？
What do you think of a chair like this?
很自信
It's assertive.
哦 还有气腰
Oh, and it's got air lumbar.
查德的腰需要呼吸
Chad's lumbar do be needin' air.
好悲伤
Good grief.
钱德勒 你觉得这个怎么样？
Chandler, what do you think of this?
哇哦 你们都听到了吗？
Whoo-hoo, did you all hear that?
乔伊 你能给我们做个爆震测试吗？
Joey, can you give us the knock test?
是 啊
Yeah.
再见 这就是我们带乔伊来的原因
See you guys, this is why we brought Joey.
他非常乐于助人
He's incredibly helpful.
实际上我刚给我妈妈买了这台电视
I actually just bought my mom this TV.
你觉得怎么样 乔伊？
What do you think of it, Joey?
这是一台好电视
It's a nice TV.
我们来吧
Let's do it.
我们有电视 有书摊 还有椅子
We have a TV, we have a bookstand, and we have a chair.
我们再拿一台电视机
Let's grab another TV.
这个里面有罗库
This one has Roku in it.
我想我们可以走了
I think we're good to go.
他是我们多米诺骨牌的人
He's our Domino's guy.
我们把他带到任何地方
We just bring him everywhere.
你觉得你今天会这样做吗？
Did you think you would be doing this today?
不 我没有
No, I didn't.
完全？-没有
At all?- No.
所以总共是2360美元
So the total is 2, 360 dollars.
比我想象的要少
Way less than I thought.
所以我们把家具做了
So we got the furniture sort of done.
是 啊 -好吧 我们有个U型运输机
Yeah. - All right, we got a U-Haul
为了查德家的东西
for this stuff for Chad's house.
哇哦 -啊！
Whoosh. - Ahh!
看 这就是我们带你来的原因 乔伊
See, this is why we brought you, Joey.
一整天 只要乔伊告诉我们
Throughout the day, anytime Joey told us
他喜欢的东西 我会去另一个通道 我会打电话给杰克告诉他
he liked something, I would go to a different aisle, and I'd call Jake and tell him.
杰克负责秘密买东西 所以当我们让乔伊对房子感到惊讶的时候
Jake was in charge of covertly buying stuff so when we surprised Joey with the house,
我们可以把这些对他也很重要的酷东西都放在里面
we could have all this other cool stuff that means a lot to him in there as well.
吉米打电话给我
Jimmy's calling me.
嘿 怎么了 伙计？
Hey, what's up, buddy?
嘿 所以我和他一起坐在车里 我得到了一些情报
Hey, so I rode with him in the car and I got some intel.
好吧 你有什么发现？
Okay, what you got?
我要你给他买一部最新的iPhone 一堆狗用的东西
I need you to get him the newest iPhone, a bunch of stuff for dogs,
然后他在手机上贴了一个怪物贴纸 所以给他一千个
and then he had a Monster sticker on his phone, so get him like a thousand.
给他一千
Get him a thousand.
一千？好了 准备好了吗 马库斯？
A thousand? All right, you ready, Marcus?
我们找到了 -我们找到了
We got it. - We got it.
我们来吧
Let's do it.
我们有肉汁骨头
We got the Gravy bone.
嘿 伙计们 我们有猫粮
Hey guys, we got the cat food.
他说他需要猫食 对吧？
He said he needed cat food, right?
他有一条狗
He has a dog.
哦 -他在想什么？
Oooh. - What was he thinking?
我们怎么才能得到一千个怪物？
How are we gonna get a thousand Monster?
把它装起来！
Load it up!
我们把它们都拿过来
Let's get all of 'em.
非常重要的情报 你准备好了吗？
Very important intel, are you ready?
是的 我们准备好了
Yes, we're ready.
他有一个三岁的女儿
He has a three year old daughter.
给她买很多玩具
Get her lots of toys.
哦 太好了 谢谢
Oh, perfect, thank you.
尽管你像个大块头和吓人的人 但你是个完美的男人
Despite the fact that you are like ginormous and scary, you'rethe perfect guy for this.
再见 再见
I'll be seeing you, bye.
再见
Bye.
我们是给她弄个游乐场 还是给她弄辆真正酷的摩托车？
Do we get her a playhouse, or do we get her one of the really cool motorized cars?
你不能两个都拿错
You can't go wrong with getting both.
好吧 那我们两个都做吧！
Well, let's do both then!
我觉得他有点过火了
I think he'sgoing a little overboard.
盲人驾驶
Driving blind.
我们在二号店 还有一些家具
We're at store number two, some more furniture.
克里斯 这看起来不错
Chris, this looks good.
皮革？-哦 我喜欢这个
Leather?- Oooh, I like this.
潜水感觉如何？-没有疼
How'd that dive feel? - It didn't hurt.
这两样我都要
I want both these.
哦 是的 这个好多了
Oh yeah, this one's a lot better.
一切都很顺利 他不知道
This is going so well, he has no idea.
记住 现在他正在帮我们挑选他自己家的家具
Remember, right now he's helping us pick out furniture for his own house.
你觉得这整件事怎么样？
So what do you think about this whole thing?
我觉得有点酷
I think it's kinda cool
你们都在帮助这个人
that you all are helping this man.
所以接下来 显然 我们需要一张床给查德
So next up, obviously, we need a bed for Chad.
哦！-好吧 我要
Ohh!- All right, I want it.
到目前为止我们的价格是2400美元
So far we're at $2, 400.
我想花更多的钱
I wanna spend more money.
那是第二家店
And that is store number two down.
哇哦
Whoosh.
$1 400
$1, 400.
孩子 那是个包裹 -我们还有四辆车
Boy, that's a wrap. - And we still have four carts.
看这张收据！
Look at this receipt!
我希望他们快乐
I hope they're happy.
他们应该是 我们有很多好东西 兄弟
They should be, we got a lot of good stuff, bro.
你最好别摔倒 孩子
What are you doin' better not fall, boy.
是这样吗？
Is that it?
就这样
That's it.
我们从这里出去吧
Let's get out of here.
我们现在使用手机 因为我们不能在沃尔玛直接购买手机
We're now at US Cellular because we could not buy a phone outright at Walmart.
所以我们可以给他一个新电话
So we can surprise him with a new phone.
我们正在做一个视频 我们要用一个全新的iPhone 11给一个家伙一个惊喜
We're doing a video, and we're gonna surprise a guy with a brand new iPhone 11.
这里的一切都很酷
Everything here, it is cool.
太棒了 非常感谢你们
Awesome, thank you all so much.
乔伊正在喝咖啡 他绕了一小段路
So Joey's currently getting coffee, he took a little detour,
所以我们要在没有他的情况下买点东西
so we're gonna shop a little without him.
乔伊回来之前 你们觉得怎么样？
Before Joey gets back here, how do you guys think it's going?
我觉得一切都很顺利
I think it's going good.
他不知道 -他不知道
He has no idea. - He has no idea.
不 你觉得他会哭吗？
No, you think he'll cry?
希望如此 -我可能会哭
I hope so. - I might cry.
我想他会流泪的
I think he's gonna break out into tears.
所以你说你还没有花足够的钱 对吧？
So you said you hadn't spent enough money yet, right?
我们几乎什么都没花
We've spent hardly anything.
好吧 你在这里会掉很多钱的
Well, you're about to drop a lot of money here.
我敢说
I dare you.
我们要一套五月标签
We want the set of the May tags.
我们可以买这个 上面有个平板电脑
We can get this one, it's got a tablet on it.
我花了几十万美元买些蠢货 但即使这样也太过分了
I blow hundreds of thousands of dollars on dumb stuff, but even this seems excessive.
里面有个扬声器
It's got a speaker in it.
不要紧 这就解释了 我们去拿吧
Never mind, that explains it, let's get it.
嘿 钱德勒 克里斯现在要卖了
Hey Chandler, Chris is now for sale.
你是799美元
You're $799.
你本来是1500美元 但现在打折了
You were $1, 500 but you're on discount.
是的 因为我内心有点崩溃
Yeah, it's because I'm kinda broken on the inside.
你觉得这个总数会是多少？
So how much do youthink this total's gonna be?
我想是9000美元
I would say $9, 000.
我们55岁了
We're at 55 with all that.
我们得弄个烤架和割草机
We gotta get a grill and a lawnmower.
2800美元
2, 800 dollars.
好吧 总共9586美元
Okay, your total is $9, 586.
所有的购物都结束了
All the shopping is done.
我们把它装上 然后去房子
Let's load it up and head to the house.
好吧 我们把它带回家给查德
All right, let's take it home for Chad.
你很好 你很好
You're good, you're good.
快回来
Come on back now.
我害怕 我害怕！
I'm scared, I'm scared!
停止了只是--
That stopped just--
那就是你的号码
Well that is U-Haul number one.
天啊
Oh god.
那是第二个长途电话
And that is U-Haul number two.
现在我们得把房子填满 这样明天就能给查德一个惊喜
Now we need to fill the house up so we can surprise Chad tomorrow.
让我们卸一些U形拖车
Let's unload some U-Hauls.
你在找什么？
What are you looking for?
喝点牛奶 伙计
Some milk, man.
为什么牛奶会在橱柜里？
Why would milk be in the cabinet?
没有冰箱
There's no fridge.
我们得把它放进去
We gotta put it in.
哦
Oh.
如果你想要牛奶就去拿冰箱 -好吧
Go grab the fridge if you want milk. - Okay.
哥们 查德的新台面上到处都是面包屑 伙计
Dude, you got crumbs all over Chad's new counter tops, man.
幸好我们买了纸巾和克罗克斯湿巾！
Good thing we bought paper towels and Clorox wipes!
这是很多东西
This is a lot of stuff.
我知道我们有乔伊要帮忙
And I know we have Joey here to help,
但我们还需要更多的后援
but we still needed more backup.
所以我带来了一支军队
So I brought an army.
伙计们 集合！
Come on in guys, assemble!
我们把房子盖起来吧
Let's set up this house
所以明天我们可以给查德一个惊喜
so tomorrow we can surprise Chad.
杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克！
Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake!
盒子破了！
The box is breaking!
杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克 杰克！
Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake!
我要去哪里？
Where am I going?
拉 拉 拉 拉 拉 拉
Pull, pull, pull, pull, pull.
推 推 推 推 推 推
Push, push, push, push, push, push.
休息 休息 休息 休息 休息 休息
Rest, rest, rest, rest, rest, rest.
我们明天上午九点带查德来
We're bringing Chad here tomorrow at nine AM.
所以我们要给他一个惊喜
So we're gonna surprise him then.
明天早上之前我们必须把一切都准备好
We have to have everything ready by tomorrow morning.
克里斯 你负责洗衣机和烘干机
Chris, you're in charge of the washer and dryer.
钱德勒 你想做什么就做什么 因为你是钱德勒
Chandler, you do what you wanna do, because you're Chandler.
嗯？
Huh?
我们走吧 大家！
Let's go, people!
我们剩下的就是这个漂亮的冰箱 我一直在寻找我的一生
What we have left is this beautiful fridge that I've been looking for my whole life.
这个坏小子 4 000瓦
This bad boy, 4, 000 watts.
里面有20盏灯 4个柜子和一个按钮
It's got 20 lights in it, four cabinets, and a button.
我们把它取下来！
Let's get it off!
你想明天早上我们给他一个惊喜的时候再来吗？
Do you wanna come back tomorrow morning when we surprise him?
真的？
Really?
如果他们放下割草机 查德就不会高兴了
If they drop this lawnmower, Chad ain't gonna be happy.
冰箱里一定有牛奶
There's gotta be some milk in this fridge.
当然是为了我的奥利奥
For my Oreos of course.
噢 噢
Oww, oww.
牛奶在哪里？
Where's the milk?
我的冰箱里有牛奶
My fridge comes with milk.
钱德 如果你不介意的话 他们想把冰箱放在屋里
Chandler, if you don't mind, they're trying to put the fridge in the house.
拜托 退后一点
Please, just step back.
好吧 继续
All right, go on.
所以我们低调地回了他的店 他的经理开车去拍摄
So we low-key called back his store, and his manager actually drove out to the shoot
他有话要说
and he had this to say.
所以 我们在电话里告诉你这个故事
So, we told you this story on the phone.
我们点了比萨饼 乔伊送过来了 现在他只是帮我们搬家具
We ordered a pizza, Joey delivered it, and now he's just helping us move furniture.
所以是的 最后我们会把房子给他
So yeah, at the end of the day we're giving him this house.
哇 呃
Wow, uh.
你能再多说一点吗？
So could you tell a little bit more?
因为老实说他没有告诉我们太多关于他的私生活的事
Because honestly he hasn't told us much about his personal life.
孩子不在的时候 他总是做兼职
When the kid's off he works on side jobs all the time.
他现在住在一个房东不太冷静的地方
He lives in a place right now where the landlord's not too cool.
乔伊每天要开车一小时上班
Joey has to drive an hour to work every day.
我们要给他的新房子离工作只有15分钟的路程
And this new house we're about to give him is only 15 minutes away from work.
我真的很高兴他需要它 这将真正改变他的生活
I'm just really happy that he needs it, and this will genuinely change his life.
智能电视 65英寸 4K 你知道 哈！
Smart TV, 65 inch, 4K, you know, ha!
爸 爸 别伤害我！
Da, da, don't hurt me!
啊 啊！
Ahh, ahh!
趴下！
Get on the ground!
刷牙！
Brush his teeth!
我要给你刷牙！
I'm going to brush your teeth!
I will brush your teeth!
哇 这是什么？
Whoa, what is this?
哦！
Oh!
我没想到会有那么多碎片 嗯 别人的问题
I didn't expect that to be in that many pieces. Um, somebody else's problem.
马库斯！
Marcus!
我称之为“书桌抽象”
I call it, "Desk a la abstract. "
哦 我的上帝
Oh my god.
是你干的 就是你？
You did that, that's you?
我看了说明书
I read the instructions.
他们是越南语的
They were in Vietnamese.
已经14个小时了
It's been 14 long hours.
我们买了一栋房子
We've bought a house.
我们做到了
We did.
差不多花了10万
Which cost almost 100 grand.
然后我们花了数万美元买了房子的东西
And then we spent tens of thousands of dollars on items for said house.
我一个人在洛伊家花了将近1万美元
I spent almost 10 grand at Lowe's by myself.
谢谢您！
Thank you!
看 我们没花多少钱
See, we weren't spending much.
我为你感到骄傲 你得到了加薪
I'm proud of you, you get a raise.
谢谢您
Thank you.
乔伊整天都跟着我们
Joey's been following us around all day.
不知道 这房子是他的
No idea, that this house is his.
我们买了这所房子 他将永远保留它
We bought this house and he is going to keep it, forever.
是他的
It is his.
他会穿过那扇门
He's gonna walk through that door,
我要告诉他这实际上是他的房子
and I'm gonna inform him that this is in fact his house.
我们来吧
Let's do it.
抱歉 面试怎么样？
Sorry about that interview, how'd it go?
没关系
It was all right.
是不是很尴尬？
Was it awkward?
对
Yes.
如你所知 有些事发生了
As you can tell, something's up.
我们在这件家具上花了那么多钱 连你的钱都付不起
We spent so much money on this furniture, that we can't even pay you
我们答应的几千美元
the few thousand dollars we promised,
因为我们把所有的钱都放在你家里了
because we put all the money into your house.
所以是的 很抱歉
So yeah, sorry about that.
可以
Okay.
是啊 你的房子看起来不错
Yeah, your house looks nice.
是啊 杰克 你觉得他的房子怎么样？
Yeah, what do you think of his house, Jake?
我觉得很棒
I think it's awesome,
我想他会喜欢的
I think he's really gonna enjoy it.
什么？
What?
这是你的房子
This is your house.
是的 你的房子
Yeah, your house.
哦 我们没告诉你？
Oh, we didn't tell you?
这是给你的
This is for you.
我们在乍得的事上撒谎
We were lying about Chad.
整个房子都是给你的
This whole house is for you.
乍得根本不存在 -等等 真的吗？
Chad doesn't exist. - Wait, serious?
太棒了！
That is awesome!
你是查德
You are Chad.
谢谢您！
Thank you!
是的 儿子 这是你的房子
Yeah son, this is your house.
所以我们早些时候注意到你手机上有一个怪物贴纸
So we noticed earlier that you had a Monster sticker on your phone.
所以我们给你买了100罐怪物
So we bought you 100 cans of Monster.
真 的
Wow.
然后你说你养了一条狗
And then you said you had a dog,
所以我们给你买了一堆狗粮
so we bought you a bunch of dog food.
还有一些玩具给他
And some toys for him.
我们不知道是哪个牌子的 所以我们就买了
We didn't know which brand, so we just got all of 'em.
真 的！
Wow!
我们让你想起了你最喜欢的东西
We reminded you of your favorite thing.
披萨
Pizza.
哦 哇 炉子里还有比萨饼
Oh wow, there's more pizza in the stove.
甚至不知道那里有
Didn't even know that was there.
你一整天都不知道吗？
Did you have any idea all day?
不 我没有
No, I did not.
不 你真的没有？
No, you really didn't?
我们有点担心 因为吉米让它溜走了几次
We were getting kinda worried because Jimmy let it slip a couple of times.
他就像是哦是的
He's like oh yeah.
我真的一点也没有
I really didn't, at all.
太棒了
It is awesome.
哦 是的 我们还有一些额外的东西要给他看
Oh yeah, we got a couple of extra things too we should show him.
我们买了一些玩具 因为你提到你有一个女儿
We bought some toys because you mentioned you have a daughter.
所以我们也给她买了一些玩具
So we got her some toys too.
真 的
Wow.
我知道一定是我不认识她
I know this must be I don't know her,
所以我知道 很多
so I know, it's a lot.
真的 太棒了 你们所有人
It really is, it's awesome, you all.
都是你的
It's all yours.
像这只猫头鹰 是你的
Like this owl, it's yours.
随你的便吧
Do what you want with it.
你可以扔了
You can just throw it.
扔了它？
Just throw it?
天哪 这太棒了
Oh my god, this is awesome.
好吧 还有更多的房间
All right, there's still more rooms.
我们对装修不太了解 但我们以为这是你的房间
We don't know too much about decorating, but we assumed this would be your room.
所以你说你喜欢打猎 所以我们让你去打猎
So you said you liked hunting, so we got you hunting things.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
这是最后一个房间
And here is the final room.
我知道 就一张床
I know, just a bed.
你说过你有一个游戏站 所以有一些游戏站的东西 和一个开关
You mentioned you have a PlayStation, so got some PlayStation stuff, and a Switch.
天啊 你们真是太棒了
Oh my god, you all are amazing.
所以我们和你的经理谈过了
So we were talking to your manager out there
他说你离工作只有一个小时的车程？
and he said that you are like an hour drive away from work?
对
Yes.
所以这只需要15分钟
So this will put you in only like 15 minutes.
哦 真是太好了
Oh, that's great to hear.
哦 是的
Oh yeah.
你想对镜头说点什么吗？
Do you wanna just say anything to the camera?
这些人 他们太棒了
These people, they're amazing.
好像我的身体有点发抖
Like my body is shaking a little bit.
天哪！
Oh my gosh!
是的 很糟糕
Yeah, it's bad.
我们真的骗你装饰你的家
We literally tricked you into decorating your home.
开玩笑！
Get pranked!
你会做些不同的事吗？
Would you have done anything differently?
不 我喜欢
No, I like it.
我绝不会要求这样的东西
I would never ask for anything like this.
我们住的房子
The house we were in,
那是一所可怕的房子
it was a horrible house.
很不安全 这房子真的会好很多
It was very unsafe, and this house is honestly gonna be a lot better.
对我的孩子更安全 对我们的生活更好
Safer for my kids, and better for our living.
我们想在你们给我们房子的前一天弄到房子
We tried to get a house the day before you all gave us this house.
老实说 我是想
Honestly, I was going into this
以为我刚拿到几千块钱
thinking I was just getting a couple thousand dollars
帮助移动家具
to help move furniture.
有人给了我一栋房子
Someone just really just gave me a house.
现在我们不必再担心下一步该怎么做了
Now we can stop worrying about where we're gonna go from here.
这对我和我的家人来说真的是一个很好的机会
This is really just a great opportunity for me and my family.
我只想感谢你 野兽先生诚实地回答了我们所有的祈祷
And I just want to thank you Mr. Beast for honestly answering all our prayers.
因为这对我来说是件了不起的事
Because this is something amazing for me.
这是你的新房子
This is your brand new house.
这是钥匙
Here is the key.
我真的撒谎了 我有钥匙
I actually lied, I did have the key.
这是你的 真的
It is yours, seriously.
没有绳子 没有接球 什么都没有
No strings, no catch, no nothing.
太棒了
That's is awesome.
你介意我拥抱你吗？
You mind if I give you a hug?
是的 当然 伙计！
Yeah, of course, man!
你拿到了
And there you have it.
我买了一栋房子 点了比萨饼 然后把房子给了他
I bought a house, ordered pizza, and gave him said house.
别忘了跟着我在Instagram上买merch
Don't forget to follow meon Instagram and buy merch.
如果你想参加百万美元系列赛
If you want to be entered in to compete in the million dollar series.
再见
Goodbye.